Now we can give a type-checking role for if-then-else. So
现在，我们可以为If-Then-Else指定类型检查角色。所以
the first thing to know is about if-then-else expressions is that they do not
关于If-Then-Else表达式，首先要知道的是它们不
affect the environment, and if-then-else neither introduces nor removes
影响环境，并且If-Then-Else既不会引入也不会移除
any variables from the environment, so all the sub-expressions are
任何来自环境的变量，所以所有子表达式都是
typed in the same environment as the entire expression. Now, the predicate of the
在与整个表达式相同的环境中键入。现在，
FNL30, well that should have type [inaudible]. Because that's our decision whether
FNL30，好的，应该是[听不见]类型。因为这是我们的决定
we're going to take the true branch or the false branch, But then the two
我们将选择真分支或假分支，但是这两个分支
branches can have different types. E1 just has to have some type T1, and E2 just
分支可以有不同的类型。E1只需要有某种类型T1，而E2只需要
has to have some type T2. So notice again what this is sayi ng. This is just saying
必须有某种T2类型。再次注意这是什么意思。这只是一种说法
that E1 and E2 do have a type check. They have to be type correct but we don't care
E1和E2确实有类型检查。它们的类型必须是正确的，但我们不在乎
what the type is. The type can be anything. And then the type of the entire
是什么类型的。类型可以是任何类型。然后是整个系统的类型
expression is just going to be the least upper bound of T1 and T2. Because that's going
表达式将是T1和T2的最小上界。因为那将会是
to be the best Estimate we can give to the final type of the expression given
是我们能给出的表达式的最后一种类型的最佳估计值
that the truth branch might return T one something of type T one. And the false branch
真理分支可能返回类型为T的东西。和假树枝
might return something of type T two. The rule for case expression is the most
可能会返回类型为T-2的内容。CASE表达式的规则最多
complex one we've seen so far. But really it's a glorified if then L's. And it's
到目前为止我们见过的复杂的一个。但实际上，这是一个美化的IF THEN L‘s。而且它是
relatively easy to understand if we just pull it apart. So, so let's begin by
如果我们把它拆开，相对容易理解。那么，那么让我们从
reminding ourselves of what case does. First of all it looks at E0. It evaluates
提醒我们自己案件的作用。首先，它看一下E0。它会评估
E0 and then it looks at the runtime type of E0. So, so it takes the dynamic class of
然后查看E0的运行时类型。所以，它把动态类
E0 and then it looks at the first branch. >> Let's do that. >> And what is it
E0，然后查看第一个分支。>>我们就这么做吧。>>那是什么呢？
going to do? It's going to compare the type of these [inaudible] at run time to the
要做什么？它将在运行时将这些[听不见]的类型与
type t one, and if t one is super type. Of the run time type of E O And in fact,
类型t 1，如果t 1是超级类型。E O的运行时类型，事实上，
it is the smallest of all the possible branches. It's the smallest super
它是所有可能的分支机构中最小的。这是最小的超级
type of all the possible branches. Then it's going to pick this branch. It's going
所有可能分支的类型。然后它就会摘下这根树枝。它要走了
to bind X1 to the value. It's going to give it the type T1. So combine X1 to the
将X1绑定到值。它会赋予它T1类型。因此，将X1与
value of E O. It's going to retype it as. Type T one and it's going to evaluate E one.
E的值，它将重新键入为。键入T 1，它将计算E 1。
So you can see in one sense it's a, it's a glorified if then else, we're just
所以你可以看到，从某种意义上说，这是一种美化，如果不是这样的话，我们只是
picking the best matching branch, the one that, whose type, declared type, is, most
选择最匹配的分支，即其类型(声明的类型)为最多的分支
closely matches the runtime type of E zero. And then we're going to execute that
与EZERO的运行时类型非常匹配。然后我们要执行
branch with the variable that's named in that branch bound to the type of E zero. So
分支中命名的变量绑定到EZERO类型的分支。所以
let's see how the typing works out. So first we type check E0 and we can some type
让我们看看打字结果如何。所以首先我们输入check E0，然后我们可以输入
T0, and now what's going to happen well if we select. The branch, The first branch,
现在，如果我们选择，会发生什么呢？分支，第一个分支，
Well, then, we're going to take the environment and we're going to extend
那么，我们要把环境问题扩展到
it with the new variable x one which is going to have type t one. And so we only take
它有一个新的变量x，它的类型是t。所以我们只需要
this branch, remember, if the runtime type of e zero matches t one, most closely
请记住，如果e0的运行时类型与t最接近，则此分支
among all the branches, but if we do take it, then we're going to execute, execute e
在所有的分支中，但是如果我们取它，那么我们将执行，执行e
one in this environment and we'll get back something of some type, t one prime, and similarly
在这种环境中，我们会得到某种类型的东西，这是一个质数，类似的
for all the other branches until finally the last branch, which is exactly
对于所有其他分支，直到最后一个分支，这恰好是
the same as the first one, just with the letter n replacing the number one. And so
与第一个相同，只是用字母n代替了数字1。因此，
since we don't know which brain to match at one time, it could be any of the branches
因为我们不知道同时匹配哪个大脑，所以可能是任何一个分支
that actually executes and therefore the type of the entire expression
它实际执行，因此整个表达式的类型
is just going to be least upper bound over all of the types a, of the various
将是所有类型a的最小上界，不同类型的
branches, and here I've just extendedly super bound from a binding area
分支，这里我刚刚从一个绑定区域扩展了超级绑定
of the operation a, to an in area operation a, that should be clear enough,
操作a，到区域操作a中的操作，这应该是足够清楚的，
we're just going to take the least upper bound to all of these types.
我们只取所有这些类型的最小上界。